<?xml version="1.0"?>
<GAME>
    <INTRO>
        You recently moved into a new area,one day you decide to take your dog for a walk around the neigbourhood. As you are passing by a house which seems abandoned. Your dog suddenly breaks loose from the chain you are holding and speeds off into what seems like a tunnel and disappears. You then follow your dog to the entrance of the tunnel. You are now standing at the mouth of the tunnel
        //Commands allowed:
        -enter
        -look
        -grab "item"
        -drop "item"
        -n
        -s
        -e
        -w
    </INTRO>
    <ROOM id="A">
        <DARK>NO</DARK>
        <DESCRIPTION>You have decided to enter the tunnel, after a few steps the platform you're standing on collapses and you fall a couple of meters and land in an empty room. There is no going back,you have to  navigate your way out of the the tunnel,with or without your dog</DESCRIPTION>
        <INVENTORY>
            <ITEM>Hat</ITEM>
        </INVENTORY>
        <DOORS>
        </DOORS>
    </ROOM>
    <ROOM id="B">
        <DARK>YES</DARK>
        <DESCRIPTION>There seems to be nothing interesting in this room .Move right along</DESCRIPTION>
        <INVENTORY>
            <ITEM>C;key_Rusted</ITEM>
            <ITEM>20,treasure_Bag</ITEM>
        </INVENTORY>
        <DOORS>
        </DOORS>
    </ROOM>
    <ROOM id="C">
        <DARK>YES</DARK>
        <DESCRIPTION>There is a table with a table with a number of things on it,you might need these items. There is a door which is locked</DESCRIPTION>
        <INVENTORY>
            <ITEM>*lamp</ITEM>
        </INVENTORY>
        <DOORS>
            <DOOR>W</DOOR>
        </DOORS>
    </ROOM>
    <ROOM id="D">
        <DARK>YES</DARK>
        <DESCRIPTION>Nothing much interesting here,lets move</DESCRIPTION>
        <INVENTORY>
            <ITEM>E;key_Silver</ITEM>
            <ITEM>40,treasure_Bag</ITEM>
        </INVENTORY>
        <DOORS>
        </DOORS>
    </ROOM>
    <ROOM id="E">
        <DARK>YES</DARK>
        <DESCRIPTION>Remember, you have to find your dog or leave without it if you can.There is a dog which is locked</DESCRIPTION>
        <INVENTORY>
            <ITEM>lighter</ITEM>
        </INVENTORY>
        <DOORS>
            <DOOR>E</DOOR>
        </DOORS>
    </ROOM>
    <ROOM id="F">
        <DARK>YES</DARK>
        <DESCRIPTION>You are hearing your dog barking </DESCRIPTION>
        <INVENTORY>
            <ITEM>*lamp</ITEM>

        </INVENTORY>
        <DOORS></DOORS>
    </ROOM>
    <ROOM id="G">
        <DARK>NO</DARK>
        <DESCRIPTION>Great you have found your dog it looks injured,now get it and navigate your way out of the tunnel</DESCRIPTION>
        <INVENTORY>
        <ITEM>dog</ITEM>
            <ITEM>5,treasure_Bag</ITEM>
        </INVENTORY>
        <DOORS></DOORS>
    </ROOM>
    <ROOM id="H">
        <DARK>NO</DARK>
        <DESCRIPTION>You need to hurry,your dog isn't looking good you need to find help for it,get out of thi place ASAP</DESCRIPTION>
        <INVENTORY>

        </INVENTORY>
        <DOORS></DOORS>
    </ROOM>
    <ROOM id="I">
        <DARK>NO</DARK>
        <DESCRIPTION>A scary old witch appears and tells you to surrender at-least 60 worth of treasure or she will kill you</DESCRIPTION>
        <INVENTORY>
        </INVENTORY>
        <DOORS></DOORS>
    </ROOM>
    <ROOM id="J">
        <DARK>YES</DARK>
        <DESCRIPTION>Almost there,you are starting to see a bit of light from outside</DESCRIPTION>
        <INVENTORY>
            <ITEM>rock</ITEM>
            <ITEM>*lamp</ITEM>
        </INVENTORY>
        <DOORS></DOORS>
    </ROOM>
    <ROOM id="K">
        <DARK>NO</DARK>
        <DESCRIPTION>You have reached an exit, you and your dog have survived the ordeal thanks for playing ------THE END-------</DESCRIPTION>
        <INVENTORY>
            <ITEM>key</ITEM>
        </INVENTORY>
        <DOORS></DOORS>
    </ROOM>
</GAME>